

CONTACT

Address: Postparken 58, Kastrup, 2770

Phone: +45 71593835

Email: dina.papsujevica@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dinapapsujevica/

SKILLS

- Sociable
- Empathic
- Motivated
- Responsible
- Open minded
- Very Focus on Work
- Problem-solving abilities
- Strong Customer Service Skills
- Professional Strong Work Ethics

LANGUAGES

Intermediate

Latvian: Native language

English: C1
Advanced

Russian: C1
Advanced

Danish: B1

DINA PAPSUJEVICA

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am experienced in Project Management, currently studying Full-Stack Software Development with an aim to start a career in IT.

My mission is to learn state of the art technologies and work with industries most talented people. I want to develop my IT skills to play an important role in a large, fast-growing industry.

I adapt easily to new situations and aim to expand my knowledge continuously. The open mind allows me to integrate into the team easily and be a valuable member of it

WORK HISTORY

Customer Service Representative 02/2020 - 12/2020 GLOBAL EXCHANGE DENMARK APS – Copenhagen airport

- Responded to customer requests for products and services.
- · Educated customers on promotions to enhance sales.

Sorting employee (Night shifts) 02/2017 - 04/2019 A/S GENERAL LOGISTICS SYSTEMS DENMARK - Copenhagen

- Led sorting team of 6 people. Around 8 k small size parcels were sorted every shift.
- I was part of the team who optimized processes for more efficient work.

Project Manager 12/2016 - 04/2019 ARTBERRY", Designer union - Copenhagen

- Project coordination for Ontex (Belgium). Led packaging and product design projects for international market.
- New client acquisition
- Project managing until final stage production.

Project Manager 10/2014 - 11/2016 SIA ALPHA BALTIC, Advertising agency - Riga

- Biggest client L'Oréal. Led a group of 5 graphic designers, we designed and adapted campaign materials for Scandinavian countries. Communicated with more than 70 different people on the client side. Worked on 10–12 ongoing projects at the same time.
- Led a group of business strategist, creative director, copywriter, graphic designer, digital media, and PR consultants, where we worked for clients in Baltics, such as:
 - CSDD (Road Traffic Safety Directorate)
 - Latvenergo (state-owned electric utility company in Latvia)
 - Henkel
 - 4Finance
- Handled purchase orders (PO)
- Accounting report generation

Accountant/ Office Manager AS CAPITALIA, Financing Company - Riga

- Daily office administration
- Client relations
- Invoice administration
- Assisting executives & members
- Processing daily accounting
- Project management for clients

Accountant 02/2008 - 07/2009

10/2012 - 10/2014

SIA STALKERS K, Construction company - Riga

Marketing Manager 06/2007 - 01/2008

SPA HOTEL USMA - Riga

Accountant 06/2004 - 04/2006

SIA HANSA LIZINGS, Leasing and Factoring company - Riga

EDUCATION

Diploma: Full Stack Web Development, Expected in **07/2021 Code Institute** - Dublin, Ireland

- User Centric Frontend Development (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Git)
- Interactive Frontend Development (JavaScript, JQuery)
- Data Centric Development (Python, SQL)
- Full Stack Frameworks with Django

Bachelor of Business Administration: Accounting and Finance, 07/2007 **SCHOOL OF BUSINESS AND FINANCE** – Riga, Latvia

Erasmus Program: Economics, 01/2007 **Hogeschool Gent** - Gent, Belgium

CERTIFICATIONS

DISCOVER TECH by Riga Tech Girls, 11/2020

Since July 2020 I am part of the Riga Tech Girls community where I am learning more about the tech industry, possible entry positions and get insights from experienced people in the field of IT. As a part of this program, currently I am deepening my knowledge about Project Management and UX/UI.